jojomamanbebe.co.uk 2014-06-30

# JoJo Maman Bébé Privacy Policy

When you place an order with _[JoJo Maman Bébé](http://www.jojomamanbebe.co.uk/)_ we ask you to provide us with certain personal information such as name, address and email to enable us to fulfill your order and communicate efficiently with you. We are registered with the Data Protection Act and store your data in accordance with this act. 

When you register with us, we inform you that we will use your details to send you catalogues and other promotional offers via mail, email and SMS and from time to time allow our mailing list to be made available to carefully selected companies whose products may be of interest to our customers. You can choose not to be contacted by any of these marketing methods when you register and may change or update your preferences via your account details page at anytime or by contacting our customer service department at the address below. Should you wish to unsubscribe from our newsletters you can do so by clicking on the relevant link at the base of the newsletter. In order to maintain our high standards of Customer service any calls made to our Customer Service department may be recorded for training and monitoring purposes. 

We will not sell, use or otherwise disclose, any information we hold about you to any third parties unless you have provided us with your consent to do so. However, if we are requested to provide your details to the police or any other regulatory authority we are entitled to do so. 

You have the right to ask for a copy of your personal information held by us. If you would like to see this or have any questions about this privacy policy, or the use of your personal information please write to us at 

Customer Service Manager  
JoJo Maman Bébé Ltd  
Oxwich Road  
Newport  
NP19 4PU  

Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) Technology 

The security of your order information and personal details (including your credit or debit card details) is very important to us and we have made every effort to make security a priority when you are ordering from the website. We use up-to-the-minute Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to assure that your personal information is encrypted. This ensures that your credit card details remain scrambled when they pass over the web. Your card details are not held on the internet and once payment has been validated and authorisation approved, the card details are deleted. We use verify by visa to protect your card against unauthorised use and give you extra protection and peace of mind when you're shopping with us. 

You can confirm the security of your connection to the checkout page by checking the bottom of your browser window. When the connection is secure you will see a closed lock. You can also independently check the validity of this website by clicking [here](https://seal.verisign.com/splash?form_file=fdf/splash.fdf&dn=www.jojomamanbebe.co.uk&lang=en)

What are cookies?  

'Cookies' are small text files that are stored on your computer or mobile phone by your browser (e.g. Firefox, Internet Explorer or Safari) that allow websites to do things like provide you with more relevant information and store your user preferences.  

What are cookies used for?  

Some of the things that cookies are used for are listed below:  

  * Site performance cookies: By saving your preferences, these types of cookies remove the need to reset your personal settings each time you visit the site.
  * Anonymous analytics cookies: These cookies allow us to track how many users we have and how often they visit the site. 
  * Registration cookies: These cookies are used to track whether or not you have signed in.
  * Advertising cookies: Used to make advertising more relevant to each user.

How do I disable cookies? 

If you want to disable cookies you can change your website browser settings. We have shown how to do this in two of the most popular browsers below:  

For Microsoft Internet Explorer:   
1\. Choose the menu 'tools' then 'Internet Options'  
2\. Click on the 'privacy' tab  
3\. Select the appropriate setting  

For Mozilla Firefox:  
1\. Choose the menu 'tools' then 'Options'  
2\. Click on the icon 'privacy'  
3\. Find the menu 'cookie' and select the relevant options  

For more information on cookies, please click [_here_.](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)
